silverstripe.com 2017-07-30

# Privacy Policy » SilverStripe

SilverStripe is committed to protecting your privacy. When you give us personal information, we only use it for the purpose for which it was collected, and we treat it according to the policy laid out below.

### Scope

This privacy policy covers SilverStripe's treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect on our websites. It only applies to websites which SilverStripe manages and controls, including:

  * Our company website at [silverstripe.com](http://silverstripe.com/)
  * Our open source website [silverstripe.org](https://www.silverstripe.org/home/)
  * Our documentation (wiki) at [doc.silverstripe.org](http://doc.silverstripe.com/)
  * Our translation service at [translate.silverstripe.org](http://translate.silverstripe.org/)
  * Our blogs, email newsletters, and discussion forums

### Types and uses of personal information

At certain times we will request personal information from you in connection with online registration forms, product or service information or when giving comments or feedback on the site. Providing this information is voluntary, however failure to provide necessary personal information when requested may result in certain services being unavailable to you. All personal information collected will be held by us and may be used by our employees, officers, agents, contractors and affiliates only for the purposes specified at the time of collection.

If you provide us with your contact details, we may use this information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and new services.  
By using our website and submitting our online forms you are deemed to have accepted our privacy statement.

### Examples of personal information use

When you subscribe to our newsletter, we require an email address in order to email you the newsletter. You can unsubscribe from future mailings at any time.  
When you register on the silverstripe.org website, the wiki, or the bugtracker, we require an email address and a password. In addition, you may choose to submit additional personal information for your forum profile, and you may choose what, of this personal information, gets displayed to the public. You may contact us at any time to have your profile removed.  
When you submit a comment on one of our blogs, you may provide your name and website URL if you want to add a link back to your own site.  
The SilverStripe websites require cookies to function. We don't permit third-party cookies to track your activity on the SilverStripe websites.

### Information sharing

No information about your membership, subscriptions, nor any personally identifiable information we collect is shared outside the company, with the exception of what you choose to display on your public profile on silverstripe.org.

Server logs  
SilverStripe uses server logs to ensure smooth operation of our services and for general site and application maintenance. Like almost all Internet servers, logged information may include timestamps, your client IP address (as it appears to the server), and the pages you visit. Our server logs will not be shared with any third party. We may however elect to publish aggregate statistics on visitor activity from time to time based on log information. We will never publish any personally identifiable information.

### Links to other sites and user-contributed content

SilverStripe's sites contain links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by SilverStripe. This privacy policy only applies to SilverStripe's websites, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites.  
Similarly, while we moderate user contributions such as blog comments or forum posts on our sites, we are not responsible for such content and may not agree with the content of these comments or posts.

If you have any questions about SilverStripe's privacy policy, please [contact us](http://silverstripe.com/contact)
